It looks like she got hit.
There's blood here on her clothes, sir.
We might be able to identify her.
Or maybe we already have
a record on our datebase.
It looks like Carlota has no match here.
We can't underestimate this enemy.
Do you know her?
She does look familiar.
She looks like an actress.
Kim Dominguez.
She looks like a famous actress.
Her name is…
- Kim!
Dominguez.
Santo Domingo!
Kim Santo Domingo.
Viktor sent a red notice to the Moravianos
to hunt her down.
We'll find out where Carlota is
because of her.
I want to finish her off myself.
You know your father's men
already have this covered.
Besides.
You need to rest.
You need to recover.
Because if not, your father
will come after me instead.
- You're so picky!
- Of course.
I've already prepared your room.
You can rest now.
If you don't need anything else.
I'll leave you now so
you can get some rest.
All right.
What do you need, ma'am?
Sianong?
Let's meet.
I need your help.
Are you expecting someone?
No one.
Chiara is in Prague.
Looks like you have a visitor.
Okay.
Don't!
What's going on?
Why do you have guns?
Just Sianong?
You don't know his last name?
But he's Mikoy's friend.
Do you remember the shape of his face?
Yes.
Just describe it
so we can get a clearer picture.
Okay.
He has a pointed nose, straight.
With big eyes
but they're slightly round almond-shaped.
Thick eyebrows.
Hair is thick.
His hair is dark brown to black.
And, where was it again.
He has a mole on his left cheek.
- Yes, left cheek.
- Okay.
- Really?
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm not a cartographic artist.
What's that?
I just want to know if Sianong works
for that Global Agency
for Government Operations.
Why didn't you say sooner?
Why?
You can hack
the personal files of that agency?
That's basic for me.
I actually have a better idea
for us to find out
if Sianong really works for that agency.
What happened?
Dad, why are you here?
Bro, why do you have guns?
It's better if you don't know
anything yet.
Is this about the Valtrovis?
Is this about Sis Chiara's family
being a syndicate?
Wait, how did you know that?
I knew about it for a while now.
Dad just didn't want me to say it.
But still, how did you find out?
My friend's dad told her.
His dad is a police officer.
Who's investigating the Valtrovis.
The question is…
just a friend?
Or a girlfriend?
- Dad.
You, really!
You two…
I'm just joking.
But, Bro, I saw…
Sir Kian earlier.
At school earlier, so I remembered you.
I have a bad feeling.
I feel like something bad
is going to happen.
They think our law enforcement
here in the Philippines is sophisticated.
What they don't know is
our setup here is actually very simple.
And you don't need
a sophisticated hacking system
for us to identify their personnel.
Everything here is very simple.
So how?
You just need to know
their social media account.
Like Fishbook.
Then.
We'll go to their Christmas party.
If Sianong is really there,
I'm sure you'll recognize him
once we scroll
through the pictures, right?
We'll find out if he really works
for that agency.
Looks like him and Alex
are agents working against us.
Do you know them?
Your concern is valid.
Because it looks like
the police are targeting them.
You know, I'm starting to like you.
Looks like you were right.
You could actually be a reliable partner.
I need someone like you
to navigate the intricacies of life
here in the Philippines.
The question is…
can I trust you?
Of course.
You know the one thing
that's very important to me?
And you know that.
Very well.
So let me share something
very personal with you as well.
I love Mikoy D. Pinagpala very much.
How do I know?
We just made the definition
of love more complicated.
And I realized that I really
have fallen for Mikoy.
And every time I remember that dream,
my heart skips a beat.
And I'm filled with excitement
and overwhelming happiness.
And suddenly,
I can't wait for tomorrow anymore.
Because I know
that tomorrow,
I'll get to spend it with him.
Why would you say that?
Angelito, what we're about to tell you
is important.
So listen carefully.
This is serious.
I'm working as an asset
for the government.
The syndicate that's suspected
to be run by the Valtrovis.
That's her car.
Park over there.
Clear here too.
So my suspicion was right.
I just didn't expect it would
happen to me too.
But first, start by giving me information
that I can use against them.
Before I talk, I want something in return.
You've broken plenty of laws too.
More like a saint with horns.
Maybe you forgot,
you tried to kill me.
Just like you.
But it depends on the information
you'll give me.
If it's something useful that
I can use against the Moravianos,
maybe we can work something out.
I know a lot.
We can start with how Viktor took
the throne of the Moraviano syndicate.
Viktor wasn't favored
in the world of the Mafia.
La Morte Bianca.
She was the one who gave Viktor
his newfound power.
La Morte Bianca didn't just
protect the Valtrovis.
I'm grateful for your history lesson.
But that's not what I need.
Not a single thing in your story
gave me information
about how to take down the Moravianos.
You sounded so confident earlier
you said you knew a lot.
And now you're telling me
you don't have all the answers?
I know someone who has
the answers you're looking for.
Doesn't it make you wonder?
What Viktor gave La Morte Bianca
in exchange
for all that protection and power?
In the world of the mafia
it's always about blood.
Chiara.
La Fornarina.
Chiara Valtrovi.
How can you be so sure
that Chiara is La Fornarina?
And I can see in your eyes
that you believe what I'm saying.
I can't just believe words alone
especially coming from you.
I was right all along.
Viktor didn't believe me at first.
Turns out I was right.
What do you mean?
My initial report to Viktor
was that Mikoy is a spy.
He's working with police
officers like you.
What?
Sooner or later, he'll find out
that the two of you are connected.
And when that happens,
Mikoy will be dead.
Ma'am.
I know I'm not in the position
to say this, but
Mikoy,
being friends with a police agent,
is not definitive.
Believe it or not, ma'am.
I'm the last person who would fool you.
All I'm saying is, you're right.
Love is giving someone a chance
to explain themselves.
You probably have nothing to lose
if you hear his reason about
why he did the things he did, right?
Like John Lloyd said,
or was it Papa Piolo?
It's Alex.
The agent handling me.
But she specifically told me
to never answer this phone
until she was sure it was safe.
And now she's calling herself.
That can only mean one thing,
something bad happened.
What are you waiting for?
Answer it.
Mikoy's phone is active.
Do you want me to kill it?
No.
You said it yourself.
So maybe this is
the answers to my questions, right?
Yes.
Why are you calling?
Didn't you say
I shouldn't answer this phone?
This is urgent and I need
to talk to you right away.
Why? What's wrong?
Mikoy, listen to me carefully.
You need to stay away from Chiara.
Wait, what are you talking about?
What do you mean in danger?
- Your brother…
- I understand, Dad.
No one should know about
this, not even your mother!
I'm the one who decided
to get into this mess.
So I hope you will trust me
that I can stand by this decision.
And about Mom,
if there's something
bad that will happen to me,
at least I know the two of you
are there for her.
The agent escaped from us.
You all are stupid!
I will make sure that
everyone who betrayed me will pay!